Almen
Almen Cathedral
That Prismer looks really tough!
They were able to defeat it,
but they couldn't move it,
so they ended up building this
cathedral to keep watch over it.
You think if we melted the ice
like we did with Lyn, it'd start moving?
Quiet, Chris!
If you say weird stuff here,
they'll arrest you!
But... But...
It's frozen, but I can still feel some kind
of power pulsing within it!
It might not be dead!
I just said...
You there!
It's nothing!
She's just a little weird...
They say magicite beasts
have appeared in town.
It's dangerous, so stay here!
Magicite beasts?
I can't wait!
Rani, catch up when you can!
Aww, Chris, c'mon!
She's usually not this worked up...
Hurry! Over here!
This way!
You can tell they built this town
to keep watch over the Prismer.
It certainly has no shortage of knights!
Wow!
Reborn
to Master the Blade
From Hero-King to Extraordinary Squire
Episode 5    Royal Knights' Academy
You fool!
It's suicide to try and fight a magicite
beast with no Rune or Artifact!
I can tell from how she moves that she's
spent no small amount of time training.
Don't throw your life away!
A Greater Rune?
The same as Rani?
Th-Thanks! I'll be okay, though!
They're coming!
Fall back!
I'll cut them all down at once!
Oh? Very good!
Are you hurt? You need to find shelter!
Behind you!
It's no good!
Now, take this!
Stupid little thing...
I'll help you!
She's fast!
Now! Hit it!
O-Okay!
I'll keep going!
Nice!
You too...
I guess you didn't need my help before.
Sorry.
What's your name?
Inglis Eucus.
I'm Leone. Leone Olfa.
Olfa? I've heard that name before...
Let's work together.
Right, Leone.
Let's get to it!
One, two, three!
Nice, a clean hit!
Rani!
Chris! You ran off and left me!
I guess that was the last of them.
This is Leone.
We ran into each other and teamed up.
Thanks. You were a big help.
Thank you! I'm Rafinha Bilford.
Nice to meet you!
"Bilford"?
Then, you're Master Rafael's younger sister?
You know Brother Raf?
Y-Yes.
He's been very good to me.
You three.
Thanks for helping protect the town.
We'd like to offer you a small reward...
Isn't that great, Chris and Leone?
Just you two.
We've got nothing to give a clan of traitors.
Traitors?
Wait! Leone helped too!
It's okay, Rafinha.
Go without me.
No! It doesn't make sense!
You don't seem to know, so I'll fill you in.
That woman is the sister of Leon Olfa,
a former holy knight who
betrayed this country and fled.
Leon Olfa...?
That explains where
I'd heard the name before.
If you're seen together,
people will start to talk.
Now, we can give you that
reward over there...
No, thank you!
I don't need any reward
from the likes of you!
What's going on here?
Master Rafael!
It's just the traitorous knight's sister.
You don't need to worry about her...
Rafael  Age 23
Please don't talk about Leone like that.
She helped with the magicite
beasts again, didn't she?
You could give her a little cred—
Brother Raf!
Rani?
Is that you, Rani?
I never thought I'd see you here.
It's been a long time, cousin.
He's grown into a fine young man.
Y-You've become such a pretty lady.
I didn't recognize you.
Oh, Rafael almost never has
anything nice to say about girls.
Girls love him, but he's incredibly dense.
S-Stop it, Ripple...
This is Ripple.
One of our nation's Hyral Menases,
alongside Eris.
Nice to meet you!
A Hyral Menas?
I bet she's strong!
What are you two doing here?
Also, you know Leone?
Well...
Are you hungry?
We can talk about it over a meal!
I'm always up for food!
Come with us too, Leone.
I need to thank you for helping the girls.
So all that happened in Nova?
I'd heard their magistrate went missing.
But I can't believe you two survived a
meeting with the Bloodchain Brigade's leader.
What I'm most curious about
is the Levitation Circle.
You knew about it, and you still handed
the city over to the Highland?
If you did, I think that's
a problem, Brother.
Yeah, you're right.
So it's not just Rafael. You two agree, huh?
And that's the magistrate,
who's now a magicite beast?
She's cute.
It's hard to believe she's a magicite beast!
She shouldn't be in there!
Please, do something!
S-Sorry.
She likes girls with big breasts.
Hooray! It's not just me anymore!
What was with that knight, though?
He didn't need to be such a jerk.
It happens all the time.
But you still fight to
protect the townspeople?
You can't worry about that stuff
when the magicite beasts are attacking.
Yeah, you're right!
I respect that!
Thank you.
But don't be too hard on the townspeople.
They just expect a lot out
of holy knights, that's all.
Everyone was so proud of my brother because
he was the first holy knight from our town.
And then he killed not only
a Highlander emissary,
but even the inspector from the capital.
Wait. Lord Shiony, the inspector, was...
So they told the public
that it was all Leon's doing.
But doesn't that make him out
to be a really bad guy?
He was only mad because of what Rahl did!
You met my brother?
Y-Yeah.
He was easy to talk to and a lot of fun.
He wasn't a bad person.
Yeah, I agree completely.
Thank you for saying that.
But it's okay...
Prince Wein and Rafael explained everything,
and they even apologized.
I know an apology doesn't come
close to making things right...
No matter how it happened,
it's still true that my brother cast aside
the title of holy knight and this nation.
Leone...
So I'm going to become a full-fledged knight
and capture him.
If you need to become a full-fledged knight,
does that mean...
She's going to the knights' academy
in the capital city.
Really?
So are we!
You are?
That's great.
If I'm with you...
What a coincidence!
This'll be the start of a long friendship!
It sure will!
Yeah!
I'm hoping they can solve the problem
of the magicite beasts appearing in town.
They just appear all of a sudden in town?
That's strange.
The place is well-guarded.
It's been happening a lot lately.
They just show up in the middle of
the city without any Prism Flow...
You don't need to worry about that, Leone.
We think the frozen Prismer is what's
been drawing the magicite beasts.
So...
So if you carry it somewhere else,
they'll stop appearing in town.
What a sight, huh?
I didn't know Flying Gears could do that!
What did you want to talk about?
You're the crazy-powerful girl
Eris told me about, right?
Eris told you about me?
We're keeping it a secret between us
Hyral Menases for now, though.
Thank you very much.
So, whaddya think? Can you beat it?
Nobody fights to lose.
The truth is, it was the one who
locked itself inside that ice.
This was decades ago.
I saw it with my own eyes.
I heard once that Hyral Menases
have long lifespans, but...
I'm actually quite the old lady.
So's Eris.
Actually, though, I'm an old man...
We tell everyone it's a corpse
so they don't get scared.
What's happened lately is a sign
that it'll soon revive.
So you're carrying it near the border,
and away from any cities, in case it does?
And not only that, you're using
the magicite beasts it creates
as a defense against invasion
by enemy countries...
You look upset.
It's a waste!
The magicite beasts and invading armies
will destroy each other!
But this is a great spot to fight a Prismer
without worrying about the surroundings.
Yup! It's nice to see you're
looking at this optimistically.
Of course!
Make sure you call me when it happens!
Let's make a pinky promise, then.
Ripple and I will stay here to supervise
the transport, so this is goodbye.
We're sending this Flying Gear Port
back to the capital. You can ride it there.
Please revive soon, so we can
fight to our hearts' content!
Capital City Kyral
And on the day we started at the school...
We welcome you to the
Royal Knights' Academy.
Prince Wein
Everyone here has been chosen
to become a knight
Principal Miliera
in order to protect our nation
of Caralia and its citizens.
Study hard, and keep
your honor and the weight
of the responsibility you bear
in your hearts at all times.
Hello, everyone!
I'm Miliera, your principal!
Nice to meet you all!
That's the principal?
Look carefully.
A Special-class Rune!
Just like Brother Raf. Which means...
She's strong enough to be a holy knight.
Did you hear the rumor about
one of the new students?
The little sister of a Highlander-killer?
Is that true?
The principal's talking, okay?
But nobody's got time for long speeches,
so let's begin the orientation!
Let's start with warm-ups!
What?
An earthquake?!
Everyone in the knights' class,
I trust you've left your Artifacts behind?
Yes!
I have!
Then...
What is this?
My body's so heavy...
This is a powerful gravity field
generated by my Artifact.
You'll do your combat training inside it!
It makes me sad when my students
die on the battlefield,
so I'm going to train you as
hard as I possibly can, okay?
This is great! I love this school!
This is rough without an Artifact.
It's good training, though!
Okay, here we go!
Time to play a game of tag! They're "it"!
If you can avoid being
tagged for ten minutes,
you get a whole month's
free food at the cafeteria!
That'd be a lifesaver!
We have to win, then!
But I feel so heavy!
Don't worry, Rani.
Then without further ado...
Ready... and go!
Haah!
Take that!
And that!
Phew... There we go!
Hooray!
A month of all the free food we can eat!
You're amazing, Inglis!
Does that mean...
Nobody got tagged, so...
We all get free food for a month?
What you just saw was a demonstration
that knocking them...
out of the ring doesn't count!
Ma'am, I don't think that's fair.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I messed up.
One more time, please!
That was also a demonstration, okay?
You know, it's so important
I had to show you twice!
Listen. I'll give you three free months if
you stop throwing my golems outside the ring!
Give it to the three of us, and it's a deal.
Very well. A bargain has been struck!
Now, let's try this again.
Ready, go!
Ninety seconds left.
Four knights and one squire remain.
I-It's coming!
Get away!
Don't push me, Pram!
I'm sorry, Rati!
It won't be that easy to
defeat Liselotte Arcia!
Sixty seconds left!
You're almost there!
I'm increasing the gravitational pull!
Wow!
This is great!
I can't take it anymore...
I c-can't move!
You're so heavy! I'm going to die!
Don't you dare touch me!
Last one standing!
It's over!
She's so strong!
Is she a squire?
She was so amazing back there!
She's pretty, too.
All done!
Inglis gets the free meal tickets, then!
How fascinating!
I'd love to ask you all kinds of questions.
S-Sure, as long as you keep your promise.
The food in the cafeteria was so good!
And we get to eat as much as we want! Wow!
The desserts were great, too!
Leone should've stayed for dessert
instead of heading back alone.
I told you, I can't stay in a room like this.
I'm supposed to trust the sister of a
holy knight who betrayed his country?
Why was she even allowed to enroll?
Well, the academy decided there
was nothing wrong with her...
And I'm saying that decision was wrong!
The least you can do is reassign her
to a different room!
Very well.
Would anyone like to switch rooms?
Okay! Come to our room, then!
You're all so mean!
She fought the magicite beasts
to protect the people of Almen!
Even when they said awful things
about her, she never complained!
A girl like that can't be a bad person!
Rani, calm down.
We'll have three people in our room.
Let's go, Leone.
I'm sorry this keeps happening.
I still think I should sleep on the floor.
It's fine. We can sleep in the same bed.
Me too, then!
We can all sleep in the same bed!
Thank you both!
She sure fell asleep fast.
It's her first day at school.
She's tired.
It's been so long since I slept in
the same bed as someone else.
You're not alone.
We're with you.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Inglis...
ZZZZWFARGGHHHZZZZZ
m 151 19 l 187 9 206 37 198 179 197 218 151 217
A construction
site?!
Comic by Kuromura Moto